<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thoughts on My Little Stories</title>
    <link>https://sivaprasadreddy.github.io/tags/thoughts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thoughts on My Little Stories</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sivaprasadreddy.github.io/tags/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The ugly truth</title>
      <link>https://sivaprasadreddy.github.io/posts/2019/06/the-ugly-truth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sivaprasadreddy.github.io/posts/2019/06/the-ugly-truth/</guid>
      <description>I am so excited to meet my old friend Vinay after a long time. It has been almost one and half year we spoke to each other. We worked together in one of my previous organizations and he is a close friend and kind of mentor to me too. We both got busy in our lives and we are not in touch lately. I am so happy to meet him after a long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From &#34;OMG, I don&#39;t have enough time&#34; to &#34;I am getting bored&#34;</title>
      <link>https://sivaprasadreddy.github.io/posts/2019/05/from-busy-to-bored/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sivaprasadreddy.github.io/posts/2019/05/from-busy-to-bored/</guid>
      <description>Few months ago&amp;hellip; Its Saturday. I woke up at 5.30 AM as usual. I know exactly what to do today because I usually plan what I will do next day. Today I planned to learn about AWS and Terraform.
Todo List
1. Learn AWS &amp;amp; Terraform  After morning routine activities I was skimming through my Twitter timeline. Somebody posted a link to his blog post about Azure which is gaining more popularity in recent times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every option comes with pros and cons</title>
      <link>https://sivaprasadreddy.github.io/posts/2019/02/every-option-comes-with0pros-and-cons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sivaprasadreddy.github.io/posts/2019/02/every-option-comes-with0pros-and-cons/</guid>
      <description>We want better. We always want to get better things in life..better job, better house, better living standards etc. In the process of getting better we pursue new career options, make new life choices. And, we hope with our new choices our life will get better.
But, most of the times we forget one thing.
 Every choice we make might bring some positive things into our life and also bring some new challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whom you like the most?</title>
      <link>https://sivaprasadreddy.github.io/posts/2018/whom-you-like-most/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sivaprasadreddy.github.io/posts/2018/whom-you-like-most/</guid>
      <description>I was doing my under graduation in 2001. One day the lecturer was absent and we were all talking loud, making lot of noise. Then our correspondent came to the class to engage.
He asked us one question Whom do you like the most?
Each of us gave different answers such as &amp;ldquo;I like Megastar Chiranjeevi&amp;rdquo;, I like &amp;ldquo;My mother&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;I like Sridevi&amp;rdquo; etc etc.
After all the students expressed who is their favorite person, he said So, none of you like yourself!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>