<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on My Little Stories</title>
    <link>https://sivaprasadreddy.gitlab.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on My Little Stories</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sivaprasadreddy.gitlab.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>From &#34;OMG, I don&#39;t have enough time&#34; to &#34;I am getting bored&#34;</title>
      <link>https://sivaprasadreddy.gitlab.io/posts/2019/05/from-busy-to-bored/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sivaprasadreddy.gitlab.io/posts/2019/05/from-busy-to-bored/</guid>
      <description>Few months ago&amp;hellip; Its Saturday. I woke up at 5.30 AM as usual. I know exactly what to do today because I usually plan what I will do next day. Today I planned to learn about AWS and Terraform.
Todo List
1. Learn AWS &amp;amp; Terraform  After morning routine activities I was skimming through my Twitter timeline. Somebody posted a link to his blog post about Azure which is gaining more popularity in recent times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every option comes with pros and cons</title>
      <link>https://sivaprasadreddy.gitlab.io/posts/2019/02/every-option-comes-with0pros-and-cons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sivaprasadreddy.gitlab.io/posts/2019/02/every-option-comes-with0pros-and-cons/</guid>
      <description>We want better. We always want to get better things in life..better job, better house, better living standards etc. In the process of getting better we pursue new career options, make new life choices. And, we hope with our new choices our life will get better.
But, most of the times we forget one thing.
 Every choice we make might bring some positive things into our life and also bring some new challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whom you like the most?</title>
      <link>https://sivaprasadreddy.gitlab.io/posts/2018/whom-you-like-most/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sivaprasadreddy.gitlab.io/posts/2018/whom-you-like-most/</guid>
      <description>I was doing my under graduation in 2001. One day the lecturer was absent and we were all talking loud, making lot of noise. Then our correspondent came to the class to engage.
He asked us one question Whom do you like the most?
Each of us gave different answers such as &amp;ldquo;I like Megastar Chiranjeevi&amp;rdquo;, I like &amp;ldquo;My mother&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;I like Sridevi&amp;rdquo; etc etc.
After all the students expressed who is their favorite person, he said So, none of you like yourself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Movies</title>
      <link>https://sivaprasadreddy.gitlab.io/posts/2018/my-favorite-movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sivaprasadreddy.gitlab.io/posts/2018/my-favorite-movies/</guid>
      <description>My Favorite Hollywood Movies I am a big fan of Quentin Tarantino and I love all of his movies. But the following movies are top notch in my opinion and I never get bored of watching them.
 Pulp Fiction Django Unchained Kill Bill: Volume 1 Kill Bill: Volume 2 Inglourious Basterds The Hateful Eight  Next, I am huge fan of Clint Eastwood and I love his movies too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debugging Weird Technical Issues using Siva&#39;s 3-Step Debugging Law</title>
      <link>https://sivaprasadreddy.gitlab.io/posts/2017/01/debug-3-laws/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sivaprasadreddy.gitlab.io/posts/2017/01/debug-3-laws/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At times we stuck with some weird problem which doesn&amp;rsquo;t make any sense and gives no clue where to start debugging the issue also.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you find yourself in that situation, follow the following 3 steps.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my new personal blog</title>
      <link>https://sivaprasadreddy.gitlab.io/posts/2017/01/helloworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sivaprasadreddy.gitlab.io/posts/2017/01/helloworld/</guid>
      <description>Hi,
My name is Siva and by profession I am a Software Developer. I do blog about the technology stuff that I learned at http://sivalabs.in.
I wanted to start blogging about non-technical stuff and here I am with my new blog https://sivalabs.gitlab.io/.
Going forward you can find my thoughts on various interesting things in life here.
Stay tuned :-)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>